The rain is falling and you feel all alone. Just
remember I'm here. You can call me on the phone
Cause we're always there together And in any
kind of weather We don't have to hide We're
walking side by side Side by
side
The world can be a lonely place A fast and hurried
crazy race Though we can slow it down a while It's
always better when I see you smile Cause we're
always better together In any kind of weather We
don't have to hide We're walking side by side
Side by side
Through the highs, through the lows, that's
just the way it goes.
We're always better together In any kind of
weather We don't have to hide We're walking side
by side
Side by side Side by side
Side by side